{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3b408b4a06bef1da78c"},"product_asin":"B07MHXGXTW","QAs":[{"question":"Is it side open?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"pat","date":"2021-03-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it side open?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Included pant or not????","answer":"Only kurta, no bottom wear","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with lining?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-12-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I return it?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lining is there","answer":"Yes it has a lining","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pant will come with the kurti or not","answer":"No pants.Only kurta.","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this stiched?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Sujata Roy","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3b408b4a06bef1da79a"},"product_asin":"B07V6CZZTL","QAs":[{"question":"Is the design printed or woven ?","answer":"Printed","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it transparent? Is the cloth having netted fabric or woollen fabric like appearance?","answer":"No, it is not transparent. My wife finds it elegant and quite trendy plus value for money.Has a knitted fabric look.","votes":"0","username":"RMIyer","date":"2021-02-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Printed kurti?","answer":"Print very nice","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a winter kurta","answer":"Colour and print very nice","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3b708b4a06bef1da7a0"},"product_asin":"B09BD123Z1","QAs":[{"question":"Which size to take for chest 40?","answer":"42 will be best","votes":"0","username":"Swarna","date":"2023-01-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3c108b4a06bef1da7b4"},"product_asin":"B099NBTRBD","QAs":[{"question":"Is this printed design or the embroided all over the top?","answer":"Zari oven in front of kurta","votes":"0","username":"G.Parvathi","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3c708b4a06bef1da7c0"},"product_asin":"B083YKPKLL","QAs":[{"question":"What is site 12? Size L?","answer":"Yes 12 size is L","votes":"0","username":"SHRUTI SINHA","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 100% cotton or cotton blend/mix?","answer":"Yes .it is 100% cotton.","votes":"0","username":"Reeta.Vad","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"doeS It has side pockets?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Parvinder","date":"2020-12-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pl.give colour name?","answer":"Rani pink","votes":"0","username":"Meenal Upreti","date":"2020-10-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Buttons openable?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"deepti","date":"2020-09-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there pocket in the kurti??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Parvinder","date":"2020-12-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it is come with plazzo?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Jaya","date":"2020-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this shrink after wash? Please confirm","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"deepti","date":"2020-09-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"100 cotton or mixing","answer":"100% cotton","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Gautam","date":"2020-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Refund policy?","answer":"30days","votes":"0","username":"Parvinder","date":"2020-12-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3ca08b4a06bef1da7d3"},"product_asin":"B083YL3DYJ","QAs":[{"question":"Is this made of 100% cotton or cotton blend?","answer":"Yes it's cotton. Not sure whether it's 100% though. Ok kind of material.","votes":"0","username":"Rekha","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3d408b4a06bef1da7e7"},"product_asin":"B083YKV9CV","QAs":[{"question":"It's original kurta from W","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anjali","date":"2020-12-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f3d708b4a06bef1da7ea"},"product_asin":"B083YKXJ6Y","QAs":[{"question":"Is it cotton","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hemanga","date":"2021-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get pant also?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Hemanga","date":"2021-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it front open","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Hemanga","date":"2021-05-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f43008b4a06bef1da890"},"product_asin":"B08358W4MP","QAs":[{"question":"Will the dress shrink after wash?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-12-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is size L in this brand?","answer":"36","votes":"0","username":"Shivanand","date":"2021-11-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size number is medium?","answer":"34","votes":"0","username":"Shivanand","date":"2021-11-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f43008b4a06bef1da894"},"product_asin":"B07TYLMC7V","QAs":[{"question":"What is the size of dress  no option to select the size ?","answer":"Select Option h","votes":"0","username":"RAJANI MEEL","date":"2020-12-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f43408b4a06bef1da8a3"},"product_asin":"B084CJMHZ7","QAs":[{"question":"what is the colour","answer":"Blue as shown in picture.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size chart is not available is it possible to have a size chart?","answer":"See size chart on w official site","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-05-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f43608b4a06bef1da8a9"},"product_asin":"B0822RM84G","QAs":[{"question":"Does the pant have elastic?","answer":"Yes, the back side has a portion of elastic","votes":"0","username":"Bijoli","date":"2022-12-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 3 piece set or top and pant","answer":"Top and pant with dupatta","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-09-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a lehenga choli set or what because description and picture shown are different","answer":"It is not lehenga choli set","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-09-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f46508b4a06bef1da907"},"product_asin":"B083YL4MDR","QAs":[{"question":"Does it shrinks after wash ?","answer":"It doesn’t shrink","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2023-01-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much its length","answer":"IT'S BELOW KNEE BUT NO TOO LONG. GOOD STUFF. WORTH FOR MONEY","votes":"0","username":"VARGHESE","date":"2021-02-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f46908b4a06bef1da915"},"product_asin":"B08T1K7WJ1","QAs":[{"question":"Is it sleeveless dress?","answer":"Yes it is but you get extra sleeves.","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep singh","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we get sleeves to attach later?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep singh","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f46d08b4a06bef1da91a"},"product_asin":"B09NP726YR","QAs":[{"question":"Will I get the whole set or is the price only for kurti?","answer":"Kurta and dhoti","votes":"0","username":"Nadirah","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f47208b4a06bef1da92b"},"product_asin":"B08359X7C4","QAs":[{"question":"Is it transparent","answer":"It has got a lining to it. Not very transparent","votes":"0","username":"Mrudula…","date":"2022-03-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4b608b4a06bef1da9a6"},"product_asin":"B08T1JDY6X","QAs":[{"question":"Is this ready suit or suit clothes that we have to tie up ??","answer":"It is a ready to wear top","votes":"0","username":"Suneela","date":"2022-02-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4b808b4a06bef1da9ab"},"product_asin":"B08KQVWH88","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have a side pockets","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Arjuman","date":"2021-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size 38 means bust size 38???","answer":"No it doesn't have a side pocket","votes":"0","username":"Arjuman","date":"2021-05-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4bd08b4a06bef1da9b5"},"product_asin":"B08T17GMY5","QAs":[{"question":"Shall i know the length of kurta ?","answer":"Floor length","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-12-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4c308b4a06bef1da9c7"},"product_asin":"B08KQWJ76X","QAs":[{"question":"Buttons are openable or not?","answer":"Buttons are for show behind them are silver hooks which are openable","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dupatta is there","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"archana","date":"2021-05-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4c808b4a06bef1da9d4"},"product_asin":"B08359CFWH","QAs":[{"question":"Wht is the length of the top","answer":"Length is 51 inches.","votes":"0","username":"Pushpa","date":"2021-03-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Length of this kurta?","answer":"It's long..calf length","votes":"0","username":"Mrudula…","date":"2022-03-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4c908b4a06bef1da9d7"},"product_asin":"B08G2BVDR7","QAs":[{"question":"What is the size of the given product? It is Not mentioned in details","answer":"It's  xxl size","votes":"0","username":"anita Gupta","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the kurta pure cotton?","answer":"Near to cotton, not that typical cotton.","votes":"0","username":"M.S.","date":"2022-03-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the size chart measurement that of body or garment?","answer":"Yes.. little looser kind of style.. good for office and home.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-02-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"This dress for kides are dultsloo Wkz]","answer":"Adults","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Mamta","date":"2022-01-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size is best for bust size 40?","answer":"It will suitable to choose size 38 to get perfect fitting","votes":"0","username":"S chauhan","date":"2021-02-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size","answer":"My size is 34","votes":"0","username":"S chauhan","date":"2021-02-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f4ce08b4a06bef1da9e7"},"product_asin":"B08KQTK4HP","QAs":[{"question":"Does it contain both kurta and plazzo","answer":"Yes it has both kurta and plazo","votes":"0","username":"Shabnam Khatoon","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the colour fast?","answer":"No..using it since 6months","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d8f52308b4a06bef1daa87"},"product_asin":"B08T1X7JQD","QAs":[{"question":"What all items will be sent as part of suit set?","answer":"Kurta, skirt and dupatta.","votes":"0","username":"Tina","date":"2021-10-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d90ec208b4a06bef1dd6fd"},"product_asin":"B0835BC683","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have skirt or palazzo as bottom","answer":"Palazzo (flared)","votes":"0","username":"Nandini","date":"2020-06-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d90ec308b4a06bef1dd6ff"},"product_asin":"B07SXG98HX","QAs":[{"question":"Neck peice is wid kurta?","answer":"Yes, it’s pretty","votes":"0","username":"Urvashii","date":"2020-08-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Neck piece attached?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Urvashii","date":"2020-08-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the necklace with dress?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Urvashii","date":"2020-08-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63d90ec308b4a06bef1dd704"},"product_asin":"B07V5GD43Y","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have sleev","answer":"Yes, small one attached inside.","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dress  have sleeves","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"dishanaimesh","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hands cloth is inside?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"dishanaimesh","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are there pocket in this dress","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"dishanaimesh","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to select size","answer":"Size 34 will fir M size","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hands is ther","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"dishanaimesh","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether sleeves included with this dress?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this have sleeves","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this dress have sleeves?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this dress provided with sleeves to attach","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Deepti…","date":"2022-12-26 00:00:00"}]}
